(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T17:02:23.381177",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ring around the rosies, la la la, round and round, la la la la
Up and down, la la la, kokoni kite
Up and down, la la la, come here
Hey! Aren't you here early?
Wait, or perhaps... am I late?
Welcome to my 3D showcase, everyone! Thank you for showing up right on time!
I'm ready, I promise. I'm ready.
We have a lot of fun stuff planned for today. It means a lot to me that you came to see me.
Here I am in 3D for you!
I have a lot to show off today, including myself, but also this beautiful forest...
to which I call home, which I can finally show to you. I'm excited!
And if you're also excited, and you want to talk about the stream, feel free to post with the hashtag #3DKirin, which you can see on the screen somewhere.
And while I'm here for you in 3D, do you have any pose requests you would like to see from me?
I'm taking your requests right now, so you better get them in while you can.
What do you think? What do you think? I'm in a generous mood right now. I just might even do the splits for you.
Don't think I forgot. I remember. I remember.
You want to see it?
Okay, I said I was generous, but, but, am I really so generous?
I don't know, splits? Is there a way to do the splits in a... a lady-like manner?
Well, there's two methods. You can, you can go this way--that's more of a lunge, or you can go this way.
Ooh. Maybe, maybe we scrap that one. Do you have any idol-like poses requests for me?
Mermaid pose? No. I'm not doing mermaid pose. No mermaid pose.
A slap? You want to be slapped?
I shouldn't be surprised at this point.
All right, come here. Come here.
You want another one? You want another one? That wasn't enough for you?
All right, all right. I think that was enough of that. Let me show you around a little bit. Hopefully you're not too... too dazed from the slaps.
We have in my lovely forest many features, such as a fountain, perfect ASMR ambiance, lots of bubbles, mhm.
Not only do we have a fountain, well, first of all, there's so many beautiful flowers around, and this giant tree, the world tree, has finally been complete.
I built it, I built it myself, I did that. I'm nature, I did that.
We also have a bench, beautiful feature.
And a gazebo. How many hit points do you think this thing has? I bet it wouldn't even flinch if I hit it with an arrow. Very scary.
But
I think I'm not the only one in this forest.
Could it be?
Nemu, come out, come out wherever you are. You're sleeping again, Nemu.
Nemu, come out, come out wherever you are.
You're sleeping again, Nemu.
She's cute! She's cute! She's really cute!
Look at you, Nemu. Just look at you. Oh.
Hey, where are you going?
Hey, I'm trying to pet you.
Where are you off to?
Is my 3D showcase not yours? Don't get a big head.
You know I'm the real keeper of nature, right?
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Are you really just going to go to sleep like this?
You're in my 3D showcase, I guess I shouldn't be surprised at this point.
You're in my 3D showcase.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised at this point.
Do we have anybody else here in this forest?
Hmm, could it be? There's many fully grown trees around, but...
Hmm, could it be?
There's many fully grown trees around, but...
Sapling, is that you?
Wait, but you're looking a little bit different. What happened to you?
Wait, but you're looking a little bit different.
What happened to you?
Aren't you supposed to have a sprout?
Usually you're calling me bald, but today you're the one who's bald.
Usually you're calling me bald,
but today you're the one who's bald.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't look so sad. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Don't be so sad. Come here.
Oh, no, no, no. Don't look so sad.
I'm sorry. Don't be so sad. Come here.
There, there, there, there.
I will love you even if you're bald.
Incredible. Is this the power of nature?
No, you probably did this all on your own. You're pretty incredible too, you know.
No, you probably did this all on your own.
You're pretty incredible too, you know.
All right, Sapling, why don't we sit you down right here?
It's your 3D showcase too. Look at you go. Aren't you awfully cute?
It's your 3D showcase too. Look at you go.
Aren't you awfully cute?
Let me guess. That's not your preferred seat.
This must be your preferred seat.
So cute. So cute.
What a cute 3D form you have. Look at how boing boing.
What a cute 3D form you have.
Look at how boing boing.
I feel like I'm getting shown up a little bit on my own debut.
First we have Nemu looking especially cute, and now we have boing boing Sapling.
First we have Nemu looking especially cute,
and now we have boing boing Sapling.
I'm very cute too, right?
Well, thank you very much for coming, and this is not all we have.
Well, thank you very much for coming,
and this is not all we have.
Do you think I was really gonna come here and just talk to you for an hour straight?
Do you think I was really gonna come here
and just talk to you for an hour straight?
Well, that is something that I would do, but we have lots planned for today.
Well, that is something that I would do,
but we have lots planned for today.
So please stay tuned and enjoy, and let's go ahead and get started, shall we?
So please stay tuned and enjoy,
and let's go ahead and get started, shall we?
I'm back. Hello. For our first section, I would like to call some friends in.
I'm back. Hello.
For our first section, I would like to call some friends in.
Hello. Hello, friends. Are you here?
Friends here! Friends here!
Oh, hi! Oh, you're here. Welcome, welcome!
Thank you for coming to my 3D showcase. I wanted to have you guys here.
Thank you for coming to my 3D showcase.
I wanted to have you guys here.
And who might you be? Would you like to introduce yourselves, starting over, over here with...
And who might you be? Would you like to introduce yourselves,
starting over, over here with...
Irys!
Iris!
Alrighty, hi Irys! It's Irys from HoloLive English with the fellow lovely ladies.
Alrighty, hi Iris! It's Iris from HoloLive English
with the fellow lovely ladies.
Like usual, let's go! Welcome, welcome!
Looking so cute, Chloe. Hi, hi, hi.
And next we have... What's up! It's Baelz Irys from HoloLive English!
And next we have... What's up!
It's Baelz Irys from HoloLive English!
Fauna, you're so cute!
And next, who is this?
Ooh, Konichiwa! It's Ouro Kronii from HoloLive English Council, and you are so 3D.
Ooh, Konichiwa! It's Ouro Kronii from HoloLive English Council,
and you are so 3D.
I am! And so dynamic! Oh, look at that 3D! So much movement!
Oh my god! I'm going to sleep! I'm gravitating! Thank you!
And up next we have...
Oh, hi. I'm Nanashi Mumei.
Fauna, you're so cute!
Thank you! Thank you!
So cute!
Well, since I am in 3D, I wondered if you guys had any requests for me
poses or actions that you can only get right now
when I can move like this...
Ooh, poses, what should you ask for?
You have one Mumei, you have an idea.
I have an idea.
Okay, um, not so much a pose, more of an action, more of, um, acting action.
Um, could you pretend that you're in a category five hurricane?
Let's go!
Okay, like outside, not in a shelter. Yeah, yeah, like outside.
Dangerous, but you're reporting it.
She blew it away!
I guess I should be screaming.
Oh, my god.
How's that?
Amazing!
How's my acting? Mumei, Mumei, it was amazing. Very convincing.
Thank you. Thank you.
Are you next?
What you got? I want you to pretend that you are a category five hurricane.
Okay, okay.
Is this part of the tornado?
This isn't a tornado. It is similar to a tornado, but it goes to Category 5 hurricane.
I have water.
Amazing. Thank you.
Getting dizzy?
I- I- I have one.
You have one, okay. Are you going to go easy on me?
What if you were a tree in a category five hurricane?
It keeps going!
Okay, okay.
She wavy. She wavy. Oh, she's flying. She's on a truck. Oh, no. My branch fell...
She lost- lost the branch. Oh, she lost the branch. No!
Wait, is- I was thinking of asking for a pose that had nothing to do with a category five hurricane.
That's fine. But everyone's asking for category five hurricane, so...
Um, I was originally going to ask for a newborn baby pose 'cause you always, you know, 'mommy,' but- but instead, I'm going to ask for newborn baby in a...
Even the sound effects! Thank you, thank you.
That baby's kind of strong. Yeah, baby, one more kid, we can't have baby getting into trouble.
But I did not bring you here just for category five hurricanes.
I also would like to play a little game. It is a 3D showcase classic... Charades!
So, I'll be pantomiming various words which I do not know,
and they will have one minute to guess.
And that's pretty much it. Everybody knows charades, right?
So, let's start! First word!
Only Sillies don't know.
First word. Oh, is this group effort?
Group effort? Group effort. First word.
She's pointing up. She's pointing up, and then...
Now she's- Is it two words? Two words? Two words?
Is she doing what? Is she doing- Harder word! Are you a plant?
A tree? It's tall. It's tall and short. Middle and short?
She's- Oh, evolution! Evolution? No, no, no. Nature! Nature! Nature!
She dancing? Is she dancing? She's a baby. She's-
Baby getting in trouble.
And then the mother- talking to the hand. Talk to the hand. Step-daughter?
Step-mother? She crying. She crying. Someone's crying, okay.
She's so- So 3- 2- Oh, my gosh! What is-
Three called? I can't get hurricane out of my mind, I'm sorry.
I cannot stop singing hurricane.
The word was teenager!
It's a hard one! Extremely hard one!
It is hard.
I was trying- Yeah, I was trying to go for like 'height,' and I was trying to go like 'baby' into 'kid' into 'teenager,' that's like the...
Don't talk to me. Don't talk to the hand. I looked like a seed or a plant or something.
I was going to say 'made' until the 'don't talk to me' 'talk to the hand' thing.
evolution was kinda, not really
evolution
Alright, next word?
All right, next word?
Next one!
Horse race! Horse racing!
Horse racing, yes!
You got it!
That one was a little easier. Good job.
Easy.
Alright. Up next.
All right, up next.
Swimming.
Is she getting the water out of the way? What?
Pebbles throwing.
She's putting stuff. Is she cooking?
Kneading dough? Kneading dough?
Baking?
Oh, she's dead.
Oh, she's dead. Oh, she's dead.
Oh, she's yeah, she's dying there.
Wait, oh, she stabbed she stabbed. She stabbed!
Wait, oh, she stabbed-- she stabbed!
spilling out.
It's spilling out.
Her blanket's too hot while she's sleeping.
Oh, is she pregnant?
What?
Inside? Throwing? Surgery?
Surgery!
It was surgery!
That's surgery?
Good job!
That was the swimming at the beginning.
These are difficult words. All right, next timer.
Deum.
Damn.
A wig.
Is she sneaking? Is she sneaking?
Bald? Phone? Playing Hitman? Hitman, Hitman?
Oh, no.
Assassin.
Is it Matrix?
Assassin! It was assassination!
Close enough.
Assassination, close enough.
I mean, technically was I wrong? Not really.
No, the mods allow it.
It was close enough. Next next word.
Chicken.
Chicken bird?
Bird? Peacock?
Big bird?
Peacock?
Rooster?
Bigger bird? Ostrich? Ostrich?
Emu?
You say Emu? Oh, my god.
They're so cute.
She eating it now?
Chicken?
Is it delicious then?
Turkey!
Yes!
Good job! Good job!
Can you say EU again?
Were you eating the turkey? Eating the turkey?
How am I supposed to show it?
Fauna.
Dead on the ground.
Baby! Baby!
She's a mom! She's a mom!
Rock a bye baby.
Rock-a-bye baby.
Babysitter?
Oh, yes! Babysitter!
Babysitter! That was so fast!
Why did you leave the baby on the ground?
Babysitter, you got to treat your baby nicer.
Yeah, I don't know why they left the baby on the ground. I guess that
New parenting hack!
A new parenting hack!
That just don't allow the baby to hit the
category five hurricane!
Category 5 hurricane!
You got to be careful in case of natural disasters.
Hey, keep it in the house. That's what you're supposed to do.
I'm trying to say, "a natural disaster."
You're the most beautiful natural disaster.
Oh, thank you.
I mean, she she truly is making my heart go all over the place.
Doki doki?
Doki doki.
You're so cute.
Oh, thank you.
All right, next question.
Salt!
Salt! Cooking!
Cooking! She's got the salt.
Spice! Bowl!
Spice! Curry!
Shaker!
Salt Shaker
Oh, it's a salt shaker.
Salt shaker specifically.
I see.
You see?
All right, thank you guys for joining me.
I appreciate you being here to celebrate with me.
I appreciate you being here to celebrate with me. Thank you!
Thank you!
You are the goddess of the forest, it's so beautiful.
Thank you, this is my forest now.
Oh, can we eat tea together?
Yes! Eat tea!
We can have a tea party together
in the gazebo!
Well, thank you for joining me,
and up next I will be perhaps doing some performances!
You stay tuned!
Thank you! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Thank you guys!
語れない 眠れない トロイメライ
I cannot speak, I cannot sleep, Träumerei,
あなたの見てる正体
the true nature of what you're seeing.
誰も読めないカルテ
A chart that no one can read,
不思議 知りたいだけ
a mystery, I just want to know.
嘘も 真実も
Both lies and reality
どっちも 真実だったの 本当よ
were true, really!
今日も ひとりごと
Talking to myself again today,
なにも 無理をしないで わたし愛されたい
forcing nothing, I just want to be loved.
有効無効 さようなら 軽い 眩暈
Valid or invalid, goodbye, a slight dizziness.
あなたのいない現象界
A phenomenal world without you.
誰も読めないカルテ
A chart that no one can read,
自意識 溢れ出して
self-consciousness overflowing.
正しい 夢は かなしい 声は
A correct dream is, a sad voice is...
美しい？ 疑わしい？ 羨ましい？
Beautiful? Suspicious? Envious?
ねえ、 どれ？
Hey, which one?
語れない 眠れない トロイメライ
I cannot speak, I cannot sleep, Träumerei,
あなたの見てる正体
the true nature of what you're seeing.
誰も読めないカルテ
A chart that no one can read,
不思議 知りたいだけ
a mystery, I just want to know.
終わらない ことはない トロイメライ
There's nothing that won't end, Träumerei,
あなたと 跨ぐ 境界
the boundaries you cross with me.
誰も読めないカルテ
A chart that no one can read,
思春期 躓き 胸の内
youth's stumbles, deep within my heart,
不思議 知りたいだけ
a mystery, I just want to know.
正しい 夢は かなしい 声は
A correct dream is, a sad voice is...
美しい？ 疑わしい？ 羨ましい？
Beautiful? Suspicious? Envious?
ねえ、 どれ？
Hey, which one?
語れない 眠れない トロイメライ
I cannot speak, I cannot sleep, Träumerei,
あなたの見てる正体
the true nature of what you're seeing.
誰も読めないカルテ
A chart that no one can read,
不思議 知りたいだけ
a mystery, I just want to know.
終わらない ことはない トロイメライ
There's nothing that won't end, Träumerei,
あなたと 跨ぐ 境界
the boundaries you cross with me.
誰も読めないカルテ
A chart that no one can read,
思春期 躓き 胸の内
youth's stumbles, deep within my heart,
不思議 知りたいだけ
a mystery, I just want to know.
ああ、わため先輩！
Ah, Watame-senpai!
やーい！ありがとうー！
Yay! Thank you so much!
This was my first guest of my 3D showcase, my beloved senpai, Watame-senpai!
わため先輩！いえーい！
Watame-senpai! Yay!
ホロライブJP 1st generation, ホロライブEN 1st generation, つなまきわためええい！
Hololive JP 1st Generation, Hololive EN 1st Generation, Tsunomaki Watameeei!
いえーい！ふふっ
Yay! Hehe.
Thank you for coming to my forest. What do you think of the stage?
すごい！ Very beautiful place. ありがとう！
Amazing! Very beautiful place. Thank you!
お、パウナズハウス？ お？ マイハウス？
Oh, Fauna's house? Oh? My house?
お、パウナズハウス？ べりーびっぐ？ べりーびっぐな？
Oh, Fauna's house? Very big? Very big, huh?
Do you want to go? 行きますか？
Do you want to go? Shall we go?
Let's go!
We have a show, dame ka, dame ka, soka, jaa ato de, after, ato de!
We have a show... No, wait, can't? I see, then later, after, later!
いや、べりーきゅーとすりーでぃーだよ！ありがとう！
No, it's very cute 3D! Thank you!
ね、同じ色、あね、ピンク！ぴんこ！
Hey, same color, oh right, pink! Pink-o!
しろ、しろ、しろ！ホワイト！
Shiro, shiro, shiro! White!
ね、おんなじ、おんなじ、うれしいね！
Hey, same, same, I'm so happy!
かわいい！かわいい！ big face, small face...
Cute! Cute! Big face, small face...
かわいい！かわいい！かわいい！かわいい！と、きりん...
Cute! Cute! Cute! Cute! And... Kirin...
sheep, kirin... あ！は？ かわいい！
Sheep, kirin... Ah? Huh? Cute!
なになにな :！？なに！らぶらぶ！なになになにな :！？なに！？
What, what, what?! What?! Love-love! What, what, what, what?! What?!
これこれこれこれ！
This, this, this, this!
ぎゅーって一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for singing together with me, giving me a big hug!
こちらこそ！ありがとう！また歌いましょう！
Thank you too! Let's sing again!
はーい！がんばってね！ありがとう！またねー！
Yay! Do your best! Thank you! See you later!
ばいばーい！
Bye-bye!
Ah, I feel healed already. Fuwawa-sempai, she's so cute! Woo! That was just our first guest, though, and I think we have one more on the way.
Doesn't something smell a little fishy to you?
妄想がね 暴走する 超特急に 飛び乗って
Delusions run wild, jumping on the bullet train,
今 会いに行きたいの
I want to go meet you right now.
言い訳とか 理由だとか 面倒臭いな
Excuses and reasons are such a hassle,
運命だから 仕方がないよね
But it's destiny, so it can't be helped, right?
かなわなければ この恋は 永遠に覚めることもないの
If it doesn't come true, this love will never fade away forever.
何も知らない 目を閉じて かわいいままで 星に願った
Knowing nothing, closing my eyes, wishing upon a star while staying cute.
思い通りにならない 世界なら もういらない
If this world won't go the way I want, I don't need it anymore.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
All I want is just one thing—everything, everything, everything, everything!
思い通りにならない 世界とか 有り得ない
A world where things don't go my way is unbelievable.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
All I want is just one thing—everything, everything, everything, everything!
この気持ちは この気持ちにしか 分かんないのに
Even though only this feeling understands this feeling,
みんな 勝手に 決めつけすぎだし
Everyone is way too quick to jump to conclusions.
知らないのに 知ったふりで そんなに簡単に出 諦めちゃうの
Even though they know nothing, acting like they know, giving up so easily—
もったいないね
Such a waste, right?
かなわなければ この夢は 永遠に覚めることもないの
If it doesn't come true, this dream will never fade away forever.
何も知らない 目を閉じて かわいいままで 星に願った
Knowing nothing, closing my eyes, wishing upon a star while staying cute.
思い通りにならない 世界なら もういらない
If this world won't go the way I want, I don't need it anymore.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
All I want is just one thing—everything, everything, everything, everything!
思い通りにならない 世界とか 有り得ない
A world where things don't go my way is unbelievable.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
All I want is just one thing—everything, everything, everything, everything!
この気持ちは この気持ちにしか 分かんないのに
Even though only this feeling understands this feeling,
みんな 勝手に 決めつけすぎだし
Everyone is way too quick to jump to conclusions.
知らないのに 知ったふりで そんなに簡単に
Even though they know nothing, acting like they know, so easily...
諦めちゃうの もったいないね
Giving up—such a waste, right?
かなわなければ この夢は 永遠に覚めることもないの
If it doesn't come true, this dream will never fade away forever.
何も知らない 目を閉じて かわいいままで 星に願った
Knowing nothing, closing my eyes, wishing upon a star while staying cute.
思い通りにならない 世界なら もういらない
If this world won't go the way I want, I don't need it anymore.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
All I want is just one thing—everything, everything, everything, everything!
思い通りにならない 世界とか
A world where things don't go my way...
妄想がね 暴走する
Delusions are running wild,
超特急に 飛び乗って
jumping onto the express train,
今 会いに行きたいの
I want to go see you right now.
言い訳とか 理由だとか 面倒臭いな
Excuses and reasons are such a hassle,
運命だから 仕方がないよね
it's destiny, so it can't be helped.
叶えなければ この恋は
If it doesn't come true, this love
永遠に 覚めることもないの
will never fade away forever.
何も知らない 目を閉じて
Knowing nothing, closing my eyes,
可愛いままで 星に願った
staying cute as I wished upon a star.
思い通りにならない 世界なら もういらない
If the world won't go as I want, I don't need it.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
I only want one thing: everything, everything!
思い通りにならない 世界とか 有り得ない
A world that doesn't go as planned is impossible.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
I only want one thing: everything, everything!
この気持ちは この気持ちにしか 分かんないのに
This feeling can only be understood by this feeling,
みんな 勝手に 決めつけすぎだし
yet everyone is too quick to make assumptions.
知らないのに 知ったふりで
Even though you know nothing, you act like you do,
そんな 簡単に諦めちゃうの
giving up so easily like that is a waste.
叶えなければ この夢は
If it doesn't come true, this dream
永遠に 覚めることもないの
will never fade away forever.
何も知らない 目を閉じて
Knowing nothing, closing my eyes,
可愛いままで 星に願った
staying cute as I wished upon a star.
思い通りにならない 世界なら もういらない
If the world won't go as I want, I don't need it.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
I only want one thing: everything, everything!
思い通りにならない 世界とか 有り得ない
A world that doesn't go as planned is impossible.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
I only want one thing: everything, everything!
思い通りにならない 世界なら もういらない
If the world won't go as I want, I don't need it.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
I only want one thing: everything, everything!
思い通りにならない 世界とか 有り得ない
A world that doesn't go as planned is impossible.
欲しいのは 一つだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
I only want one thing: everything, everything!
全部 全部 全部 全部
Everything, everything, everything, everything!
ドキドキ
Thumping heart
っと、誰かあそこに隠れてる？
Hm, is someone hiding over there?
恥ずかしがらないで、こっちにおいで。
You don't have to be shy, come on over.
席に座って。
Take a seat.
私の森に招待もされずにお茶なんて飲めないと思った？
You didn't think you could enter my forest without being invited for tea?
さあ、もっと近くに寄って。一口どう？痛くないから約束する。
Come on, scoot closer, have a sip. It won't hurt, I promise.
ねぇあなた、やっと目が覚めたんだね。
Hey you, you're finally awake.
森に入ろうとしたんでしょ？私のティーパーティーに迷い込んで。
You were trying to enter the forest, right? Walked right into my tea party.
この森の他のすべての苗木と同じようにね。
Same as all the other saplings in this forest.
それがあなたの最初の間違い。お茶に誘われて後で大変なことになるとはね。
That was your first mistake, joining me for tea and having a hard time after.
そう、葉っぱといえば、見て。もう自分のが生えてる。
Speaking of leaves, look at you. You've already sprouted yours.
もう立派な小さな苗木に育ってるね。私の淹れたお茶は効き目がいいでしょ？
Growing into a wonderful little sapling already. My tea is pretty potent, huh?
心配しないで小さな苗木。自然と一緒に生きるの。
Don't worry, little sapling. You'll come around to life with nature.
人間の悩みは全部置いていっていいんだよ。文明、社会、そんなの...
You can leave all your human worries behind. Civilization, society...
木になればそんなのどうでもいいの。ちゃんと葉っぱの面倒見てあげるから。
None of that matters when you're a tree. I'll take good care of your leaves.
で、君はもう少し手入れが必要みたい。新しく生えた葉っぱに少し注意を払わないとね。
And it looks like you need some care. Your freshly sprouted leaves need some attention.
そうそう、道具を取ってくるね。
Yeah, yeah. Let me get some tools.
んー、何を使おうかな？
Hm, what should I use on you?
ボックスを見てみよう。
Let me check my box.
注射器？ううん。
Syringe? No.
レンチ？ううん。
Wrench? No.
バナナ？もしかしたら、メスとか？ううん。
Banana? Maybe. Scalpel? No.
ううん、ハサミのほうがいいかな。
No, scissors would be better.
はぁ、もう何でもいいや。
Ugh, I'll just grab whatever.
待たせちゃってごめんね。
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What'd you look for?
Oh, worried about these?
You know I wouldn't hurt you,
I just need to prune some of your leaves.
I would tell you to stay still, but you don't have much of a choice like this.
Here, yeah. This one?
And this one?
There, doesn't that feel better?
I'm sure all those extra leaves were weighing you down.
Oh, what about this one?
Uh-oh... maybe that one was important.
Don't worry about that little sapling, it'll grow back.
Uh, let's, uh, move on here.
I will use this brush to clean your leaves.
The, uh, remaining leaves, I guess.
Yosh, yosh. Yosh, yosh.
There, all set, too. Even if you lose all of your leaves, you must rely on me to provide you with the nutrients...
...you're now unable to create through photosynthesis.
Oh, looks good.
Now, if you want to grow those leaves back,
I think you'll need some water. Uh, but not too much.
Don't want those roots to rot away.
There. With care like this, you want to stay in the forest forever, right?
No, let me just get you one more thing.
Hey, where are you looking? Don't even think about it!
Here, here. Have a bite of this.
I'm sorry for hitting you with an apple.
There, there. There, there. You'll be okay.
Come on, I need you nice and revived so you can watch the rest of my showcase, okay?
一体この世はどうなっているのかな？
What is going on in this world?
わたしは空を飛び越えて
I jump over the sky,
地球のまわりをくるくるり
rolling around the earth.
月火水木金土日
Mon Tue Wed Thu Fri Sat Sun,
繰り返すこのバイオリズムで
repeating this biorhythm,
全自動の洗濯機みたいななんて
like a fully automatic washing machine.
そう i'm just spinning around the world
Yeah, I'm just spinning around the world.
好きにきりがないから spinning around the world
I like it all the time, spinning around the world.
時にもどかしい想い伝えたいから
Sometimes frustrating feelings I want to convey,
最近どうなの？なんて言われりゃ
how are you? What should I say?
i'm fine thank youだって言うでしょ
You say I'm fine, thank you.
グングン天狗になるわたしを
Become a gungun tengu me,
そっと側に来て叱って
softly come to the side and scold me.
愛した時からわたしが神様
Since I love you, I am God.
実際あなたの言うとおりの成り上がり
In fact, as you say, upstart.
歴史はされど繰り返す
History repeats,
はじめと終わりがある不思議
the beginning and the end are strange.
花鳥風月 雪月花
Kacho fugetsu, yugetsu hana,
巡り巡るこの季節に
in this season to go around
全知と全能をこの手にして
with omniscience and omnipotence in this hand.
i'm just spinning around the world
好きにしてもいいかな
May I like it?
欲しいものがないなら
If you don't have what you want,
それじゃ意味がないじゃない
that doesn't make sense.
隠しているんじゃない
I'm not hiding it
大事に守りたいだけ
I just want to dearly protect it
心にしまいこんだ淡い愛しさを
I hid it away in my heart, this faint love.
君の願い聞かせてほしい
I want to hear your wish.
夢の中で寄り添っていたい
Within a dream, I want to get closer to you.
ねえ 神様はきっと まだ決めてはないよ
Hey, God surely hasn't decided yet.
そう この出会いが運命でも偶然でもいいの
Yes, about this encounter if it's fate or coincidence.
ねえ 二人の間にほら 不幸なんてないよ
Hey, between us there is no unhappiness.
そう 迷う日々も どんなときも
Yes, at any time
前を向いてさ笑っていよう
I'll look forward to your lost self, now please laugh.
君だけでもしかして 全てを見抜いているのかな
Are you possibly the only one that looks down on everything?
震える子犬のような 弱い強がりも
Like a trembling puppy that weak and pretending to be strong
こんな嘘を許してほしい
I want you to forgive me such a lie
忘れないでいて 交わした約束
Don't forget our exchanged promises
ねえ 神様はきっと また願いを叶える
Hey, God surely will answer wishes again
そう 誰かのため 誰かの愛優しさの隣で
Yes, for someone's sake for someone's love, beside someone's gentleness
ねえ 二人の間にほら 希望しかないよ
Hey, between us look! There is only hope
そう病めるときもどんなときも 照れてくささ笑っちゃうけど
Yeah, at times I might get sick, at any time I get shy, even so I’ll smile
ほら 噛み合っていくよ 今 二人の想いが
Look! We will mesh it now, our feelings are,
この熱い胸も 絡む指も ずっと一緒だから
these warm hearts too, our entwined hands, forever together!
ねえ 二人の間に ほら 幸せの光
Hey, between us look! There is the light of happiness
そう 迷う日々も どんなときも 前を向いてさ 笑っていよう
Yeah, even on days we are lost at any time Let’s laugh
rainbow in the sky
青い小鳥たち
blue little birds
おいげて 輪になり 踊ろう
come on, let’s sing and dance in a circle
in the evergreen trees
夢うつつで 恋する魔法にかかられず
lost in a dream under the spell of love
風にさざめく妖精 午後は おやすみ
fairies whispering in the breeze, afternoon nap
ユニコーンの背中で
on the back of a unicorn
高いお城の塔から シャボン玉受け取ってね
from the tower of a high castle, catch the bubbles, okay?
王子様！
prince charming!
it's just a fairy tale
so it'll melt away like a lollipop
riding a flying whale
wondering when i'll wake up
お願い、ねえ、let me stay here...
please, hey, let me stay here...
ring-a-ring o' roses, fa-la-la
round and round, fa-la-la-la
flying up and down, fa-la-la
i wanna stay here forever
ring-a-ring o' roses, fa-la-la
round and round, fa-la-la-la
flying up and down, fa-la-la
ここに来て
come here
ねえ、let me stay here...
hey, let me stay here...
時計の鐘 王子様とはにかんでキス
The clock strikes, kissing shyly with the prince
ふたりはいつまでも幸せに暮らすの
We could live happily ever after
but it was just my dream
the golden sunlight shows it's time to wake up
waiting quietly, shutting my eyes and i say
お願い、もっと、let me stay here...
Please, more, let me stay here...
ring-a-ring o' roses, fa-la-la
round and round, fa-la-la-la
flying up and down, fa-la-la
ここに来て
Come here
時計の鐘
the clock strikes
王子様とはにかんでキス
kissing shyly with the prince
ふたりはいつまでも幸せに暮らすの
we could live happily ever after
ふたりを包んでた
wrapped the two of them
一日は
the day was
just my dream
the golden sunlight shows it's time to wake up
waiting quietly, shutting my eyes and i say
お願い、もっと、let me stay here...
Please, more, let me stay here...
ring-a-ring o' roses, fa-la-la
round and round, fa-la-la-la
flying up and down, fa-la-la
ここに来て
Come here
ねえ、let me stay here...
hey, let me stay here...
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
Burning Love
甘いだけなら ソルトかけましょう
If it's only sweet, pour some salt on it
誰よりももっともっと私を知って欲しいから
I want you to know me more than anyone else
さらけ出したい でもできないの 経験Nothing
so I want to disclose myself, but I can't do it with nothing as experience
モドカシ過ぎる
It's rather irritating
弱さ見せようとすればするほど ムダに強がり全てがウラハラ
The more I try to show my weakness, I act tougher for no reason
本当は私泣き虫なんだ 黙ってたけど
I'm actually a crybaby, although I kept quiet about it
でも、アマイだけの愛はちょっと 私が求めているモノとは違う
But a love that's only sweet is a little different from what I wish for
シロと言われたら クロと言っちゃう
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
素直になれない アマノジャク
Unable to become honest, I'm rebellious
スキと言われたら ダイキライだって
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろ?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
アマイバニラに ソルトかけるように…
Just like pouring salt to the sweet vanilla...
一途にスキになってしまったら 24時間7日間ずっと
If I wholeheartedly fall in love for 24 hours, 7 days a week
あなたのことを ひたすらI think かなり極端
I think about you continuously, it's rather extreme
まさか ここまで あなたにハマるとは 誰も予想なんてしてなかった
To be this obsessed with you, no one would've expected this
天気予報じゃ 当たんないんだ 恋の行方は
Weather forecasts can't predict it about the whereabouts of love
2人で一緒にいる時間に 刻まれた思い出はタカラモノなんだ
During the time spent together, the engraved memories are treasures
右と言われたら 左に曲がれちゃう
If I'm told it's right, I'll turn left
素直になれない アマノジャク
Unable to become honest, I'm rebellious
スキと言われたら ダイキライだって
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろ?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
Burning Love
アマイだけのバニラより ちょっと塩した方が
Rather than the vanilla that's just sweet, putting a little salt on it
甘味も増してゆくしね 飽きがこない…
Will make it sweeter and you won't get tired of it...
アマイだけの愛もそう ちょっと塩した方が
Yes, even love that's just sweet, putting a little salt on it
2人の距離も縮まり きっと
Will bring our distance closer, probably
今日より素敵な未来が待ってるの
A tomorrow that's more wonderful than today is waiting
シロと言われたら クロと言っちゃう
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
素直になれない アマノジャク
Unable to become honest, I'm rebellious
スキと言われたら ダイキライだって
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろ?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
甘いだけなら ソルトかけましょう
If it's only sweet, pour some salt on it
バニラソルトで バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt, with vanilla salt
甘いだけのバニラより
If it's only sweet, pour some salt on it
ちょっと塩した方が 甘みも増してゆくしね
Slightly salted, sweetness increases...
飽きがこない
You won't get tired of it
甘いだけの愛もそう
If it's only sweet, pour some salt on it
ちょっと塩した方が 2人の距離も縮まり
Slightly salted, distance closes...
きっと今日より素敵な未来が待ってるの
A wonderful tomorrow is waiting
シロと言われたら クロと言っちゃう
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
素直になれない アマノジャク
Unable to become honest, I'm rebellious
スキと言われたら ダイキライだって
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろ?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
シロと言われたら クロと言っちゃう
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
素直になれない アマノジャク
Unable to become honest, I'm rebellious
スキと言われたら ダイキライだって
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろ?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
バニラソルト バニラソルト
With vanilla salt, with vanilla salt
甘いだけのバニラより ちょっと塩した方が
If it's only sweet vanilla, maybe a bit of salt...
甘みも増してゆくしね 飽きがこない
Sweetness increases, you won't get tired of it
甘いだけの愛もそう ちょっと塩した方が
If it's only sweet love, a bit of salt...
2人の距離も縮まり きっと今日より素敵な
Our distance closes, surely
素敵な未来が待ってるの
A wonderful future is waiting
甘いだけの愛もそう ちょっと塩した方が
If it's only sweet vanilla, a bit of salt...
2人の距離も縮まり きっと今日より素敵な未来が待ってるの
Our distance closes, a wonderful future awaits us
シロと言われたら クロと言っちゃう
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
素直になれない アマノジャク
Unable to become honest, I'm rebellious
スキと言われたら ダイキライだって
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろ?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
シロと言われたら クロと言っちゃう
If I'm told it's white, I'll say it's black
素直になれない アマノジャク
Unable to become honest, I'm rebellious
スキと言われたら ダイキライだって
If you say you like me, I'll say I hate you
嬉しいのにナニ言ってんだろ?
I'm happy, but what am I saying?
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt
With vanilla salt,
バニラソルトで
with vanilla salt,
アマイだけなら ソルトかけましょう
if it's only sweet, pour some salt on it.
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt,
with vanilla salt,
バニラソルトで
with vanilla salt.
With vanilla salt,
バニラソルトで
with vanilla salt.
アマイだけなら ソルトかけましょう
If it's only sweet, pour some salt on it.
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt,
with vanilla salt,
バニラソルトで
with vanilla salt.
アマイだけなら ソルトかけましょう
If it's only sweet, pour some salt on it.
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt,
with vanilla salt,
バニラソルトで
with vanilla salt.
Ah, thank you for listening!
That song brings back memories.
We know songs from Toradora, we did... did the members watch Love Live together? So that song is special to me.
It always brings back memories and makes me a little bit emo.
But maybe I'm always emo inside.
I don't know, there's something about songs that have memories attached to them.
It brings out the feels, but maybe it's also this beautiful place that brings out the feels.
Did you like the songs I chose?
I really wanted to go for things, for songs that had like a soft effect to them.
And I was happy to be able to sing some of my favorite songs for you. I wonder if you've heard all of them.
Do you know, do you know where they're all from? They're all from anime.
But I was happy to sing them, and I was especially happy to be able to perform with Watame and Lamy as well.
So thank you too for performing with me.
And thank you you guys, because it's because of you that I'm able to stand here like a true idol.
And look, I changed! I changed from before. I'm wearing my idol outfit now.
It's really pretty. I especially love when it glows like this. I think it matches the nighttime ambience perfectly.
I really feel like a magical princess because, because look, come here, come here.
Let me bless you with my sparkles! Doesn't it feel magical? I really love it.
And I really love the nighttime version of the stage. It has completely transformed.
I might be a little biased. I think I like the nighttime version better.
It has these glowing orbs in the forest. I really wanted it to have a magical feel.
And it has beautiful glowing flowers. There might even be some glowing mushrooms.
You think they're poisonous? Will you check for me? No, no, don't do that. It's too dangerous, plus I don't like eating mushrooms. Do you like them?
How saplings learn to take all of my habits for their own, yet...
I think in this stage we also have, perhaps you've seen, dancing saplings.
Look at you, aren't you cute?
And they each have their own personalities, you all do.
Which one is you? Is that you? That you?
And the stage has also transformed the gazebo. Now instead of a tea party, we have this bed...
which perhaps I will collapse on after this is done. Ah, so sleepy.
I need to hang in there a little more. Send me your energy.
But actually wouldn't I... wouldn't I go sleep in my beautiful cottage in the background?
Maybe, maybe this is where the saplings sleep. Saplings have to sleep outside, at least I gave you a nice, nice bed to sleep on, a nice gazebo.
What do you think? Do you like the daytime version or the nighttime version? I'm a fan of the nighttime version myself.
Well, I do have one more thing to show you in this stream. You guess what it is? It would be... da-da-da-da-da!
Well, I do have one more thing to show you in this stream. You guess what it is? It would be... ta-da!
Wah! It's merch! I have more merch for you.
I wanted to make something that would be really useful. And uh, earlier this year when I came to Japan for the first time, I discovered phone rings. They're a magical invention. They changed my life.
It's starting to sound like an infomercial here.
No, you cannot skip the ad!
No, skip ad!
Um, if you're not familiar
with the concept of a phone ring, basically,
you stick it on the back of your phone, any phone,
and then you can use it to prop up your phone
anywhere you go and watch YouTube,
watch me on YouTube maybe,
or whatever else you want. Um,
it's super useful to have, little stinger.
And also it can help you hold your phone, too.
You can stick your fingers
and it makes it more comfortable.
You don't want to strain your pinky, do you?
So that is the merch that I have created for you.
I hope you'll find it useful.
It is in the shape of a cute golden apple
with a cute sapling. There's kind of a sapling theme.
It makes sense because all of this is possible
because of you guys. Thank, thank you.
Cute saplings around, cute sapling,
sap ring, phone ring!
I hope you like it,
I hope you'll find it as useful as I have found it.
Hope it'll be useful merch for you.
And so with that,
I'm afraid that our time is just about up.
But again, I really wanted to thank you,
you for being here and watching
and cheering me on.
I'm just I'm just a gaming Kirin.
But because of you, I can also be an idol,
and it has been a really magical experience
here in my forest. I'm glad you can finally see,
finally see where I've been streaming all this time.
Closet, closet is is over there.
That's where that's where I'm streaming for you.
Finally revealed.
Thank you, thank you from the bottom of my heart
for coming today, I appreciate it.
Because of you, I can be here and be an idol and a gamer,
and about my dreams, thank you, thank you.
And please don't forget to watch the other council
members' 3D showcases and watch Iris's too.
And I want to, thank you, thank you, thank you,
I can't say it enough. Thank you for watching,
and I will see you very soon, I appreciate you.
Thank you for being here. I hope you had a good time,
and I will see you next time.
Faun well, bye-bye! Bye!